

GEORGE PUSTOVIT

Full stack developer

About me

I am a third generation developer (yep, even my grandma used to code) from Ukraine with a bachelor degree in computer science who is passionate about his job. I enjoy solving business problems with the help of programming and, especially, I love to create things that live on the web. For the years spent in this field I had a lot of different experiences, so I have a solid understanding what the business needs from programmers, and will be happy to apply my skills and knowledge in your projects.

Contacts

gorapus@gmail.com

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/george-pustovit/

https://georgepustovit.dev/

https://github.com/qeorqer



+38(067) 5997407

@qeorqe

Skills

- React
- JavaScript
- · TypeScript
- NodeIS
- HTML & CSS
- · MySQL, Mongodb, Postgress, Redis
- · AWS, GCP
- Git
- CI/CD
- · React Native

- · Redux, Zustand, Jotai
- · Express, Koa
- SCSS, SASS, Styled components
- Bootstrap, Material UI
- · Next.js, Gatsby.js, Remix
- Websockets
- · Electron.is
- GraphQL
- PHP
- · Wordpress, Joomla, Opencart

Experience

Nection (11.2021 – present)

- Working as a lead developer at fast-growing startup
- Dealing with tricky tasks both on front end and back end
- · Onboarding new developers

AVA.codes (11.2021 – present)

- Working as a middle full stack developer on various clients' projects
- Finding solutions for extraordinary problems on a daily basis
- Teamed up with a lot of experienced developers

DevPuzzle (06.2021 – 11.2021)

- · Was working on a position of junior full stack developer
- · Worked a lot on front end with React, Redux Toolkit, Axios and other specific libraries like React-Calendar, etc
- Got my first experience working on backend with NodeJS, ExpressIs and TypeScript

Freelance (05.2019 – 05.2021)

- Helped a lot of people to level up their businesses
- · Created markup for web pages
- Solved business problems using JS and PHP
- Worked a lot with Wordpress, Joomla and other CMSs

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science National Technical University of Ukraine "Igor Sikorsky Kyiv Polytechnic Institute" 2019 - 2023

Languages

Ukrainian - Native Russian - Native English - Upper-intermediate